Guide to the Elizabeth S. Lyman Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Elizabeth S. Lyman papers
1958-2009
SC0224
Lyman, Jing
42.25 Linear feet
Primarily files relating to Jing Lyman's activities in community affairs, with the Women's Resource Center, and with various foundations and executive boards.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of Elizabeth Lyman, 1980.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Elizabeth (Jing) Lyman (wife of Richard Lyman, 7th president of Stanford University) was active in community affairs, the Women's Resource Center, and other foundations.
Description of the Collection
Primarily files relating to Jing Lyman's activities in community affairs, with the Women's Resource Center, and with various foundations and executive boards.
Access Terms
Lyman, Jing; Lyman, Richard W., 1923-2012.; Stanford University. Michelle R. Clayman Institute for Gender Research.; Stanford University. Women's Resource Center.; Center for Research on Women; Discrimination in housing --United States; Housing --Finance --Law and legislation --United States; Public housing.; Women--Societies and clubs; Women--United States--History.; Women--United States--Social conditions.; Women’s studies.
Collection Contents
- Papers
  - Personal and Financial Documents, 1958-74 (Box 1)
  - Fair Housing Archive, 1964-ca. 1974 (Box 2)
  - Fair Housing Archive (Box 3)
  - Fair Housing Archive (Box 4)
  - Junior League (Box 5)
  - Aspen Institute (Box 5)
  - MCFH, 1976-77 (Box 5)
  - Santa Clara County Task Housing (Box 5)
  - Urban Coalition, 1974-77 (Box 5)
  - RW/ES Lyman – invitations accepted/declined, 1970-73 (Box 6)
  - Jing: University and women's affairs; some Resource Center for Women (unsorted) (Box 7)
  - University affairs (Box 8)
  - University affairs and personal documents (Box 9)
  - University affairs and personal documents (Box 10)
  - "Jing Lyman community" (Box 11)
  - Personal and financial records, pre 1976 (Box 12)
  - Resource Center for Women, 1976-80 (Box 13)
  - Clippings on Women (Box 13)
  - Jing: miscellaneous, some letters (Box 14)
  - Jing: University affairs; miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Jing: CORO; CROW; Daedalus; Harvard Overseers (Box 16)
  - Jing: Council on Foundations and Foundation Center; Rosenberg Foundation, 1976-77 (Box 17)
  - RW/ES – miscellaneous files (Box 18)
  - Jing:
    - Resource Center for Women (Box 19)
    - Housing (Box 19)
    - Daedalus (Box 19)
    - Personal (Box 19)
  - Engagement calendars, 1974-79 (Box 20)
  - Personal and financial, 1970-72 (Box 20)
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-1990-096
  - HUB Papers-Resource Files, Series 1
    - Aagerston Associates (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Abraham & Strauss (Spirited Woman Contest) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Accountants for Public Interest--New Jersey (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Adison Wesley (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - American Friends Service Committee (AFSC) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Agency for International Development (AID) Also: Office of Women in Development U.S. Agency for International Development (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - David Alsberg (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Lenore Cole Alexander (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Allstate (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - ALPHA Center for Public/Private Initiatives: Douglas Ades (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - American Association of University Women (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - American Capital Access Inc. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Owanah Anderson (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Appalshop (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Association of American Colleges (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Association of the Bar of the City of New York (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Association of Junior Leagues Inc. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Atrium Management Group (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Auto Club Suit (Mich.) (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - American Friends of Ohel Chavah Inc. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - AWFD Referrals (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Steve Balkin (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Nancy Balfour (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Peter Bearse (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Renee A. Berger (Teamworks) (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Black Women's Health Project (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - British Petroleum (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Betty Brucker (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - California Tomorrow (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Marilyn Carr (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - CASE (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Catalyst (Archives) (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Catalyst Conference (Archives) (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Center for Community Change (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Center for Corporate Public Involvement (Archives) (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Center for Economic Policy Research (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Center for Regional Economic Issues (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Center for Women in Government (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Center for the American Woman and Politics (CAWP) (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Center for Women's Studies and Services (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Center for Research on European Women (CREW) (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Nancy Chang (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Changing Family to the Year 2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Conference on Child Sex Abuse (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - New Ways to Work-San Francisco (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Flo Ceravolo Children's Health Services (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Choice (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Citizen Ambassador Program (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Coal Employment Project - Coal Mining Women's Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Coalition for Neighborhood Economic Development (CNED) (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Coalition for Neighborhood Economic Development (cont.) (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Coalition of 100 Black Women (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Coastal Enterprise Inc. (Archives) (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Columbia News Science (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Commission on Human Rights (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Committee for National Security (CNS) (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Community Economic Developments (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Community Loan Funds (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Community Service Society of New York (Archives) (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Community News (New York) (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Community Partnerships Resource Centers (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Community Initiatives Consortium (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Community Resource Exchange (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Conference on Alternative Stat & Local Policies (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Conference on Small Business (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Update-Congressional Caucus (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Congress (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Community Information Exchange (Archives) (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut Department of Economic Development (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Cooperative Extension Service Clemson University (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Cooper Union - Continuing Education (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Corporate Public Involvement (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - CfED (Archives) (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Cynthia Couch (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Connecticut (Various Women's Issues) Senator Chris Dodd (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - CORO (Archives) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Glennis Couchman (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Council for Economic Action (Archives) (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Council for Urban Economic Development (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Council of State Planning (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Council on Foundations (Archives) (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Creative Associates (Archives) (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - CRYSTAL Quilt (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Susan Davis (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - DC Associates (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Democratic Policy Commission (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Julie DHOORE - STANDAERT (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Dodd-Blaire Assoc. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - The Door (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Downriver Community Conference (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - East Harlem Block Schools (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Eastern's Businesswoman (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Jill Houghton Emery (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Entrepreneurship Institute (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Equal Rights Advocates (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Project Esperanza (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Entrepreneurship Exchange Inc. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Equality Center (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Equity Policy Center (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Federal Organizations addressing Women's Issues (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Farmworker Center, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Federal Trade Commission (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Femin'Autres (Estelle DiDia) (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Feminist Press (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Films Incorporated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - First Bank of Boston (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Franklin Community Federal Credit Union (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Foundation Center (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Edie Fraser (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Arvonne Frazer (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Fund for an OPEN Society (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Girl's Clubs of America Inc. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Girl's Mean Business (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Mandy Goetz (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Jane Gould (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Grantsmanship - Abraham Lowenthal (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Cent-Annual REP. (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Marjorie Hart (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Hazzard Decade of Achievement 1977-87 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Lou Henry Hoover Professorship (Stanford CROW) (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Holiday Cards received 1981 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Hispanic Women Resources (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Robert Hisrich (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Harvard University (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Hispanic Organization (a guide/1985) (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Helen Hunt (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Hubert H. Humphrey Institute of Public Affairs (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Hub Econ. Development - Models of Programs (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Hub Advisory Committee 1986 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Hub Econ. Develop. (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Hope Program (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Hub's Card Collection (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - ICOSI (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Independent Sector (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - INE (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Institute for Community Economics (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Institute for Community Education and Training (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Institute for Community Investment (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Institute for Current World Affairs (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Institute for Enterprise Advancement (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Institut Frau und Gesellschaft (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Institute for Management (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Institute for Research in History (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Institute for Study of Women and Gender (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Institute of Cultural Affairs (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Inter-Agency Task Force (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Instructive TV Network (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Intergov'tl Relations and Human Resources Subcom./Comm. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - IRS Sole Proprietorship 1980 Statistics (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Investment Strategies (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Israel Voluntary Services (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Jerusalem Women's Seminar (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Eleanor Jewett (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Jewish Home and Hospital for Aged NEWS (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Cleo Glenn JOHNSON/Millie Cohen (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Johnson Foundation (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Joyce Theater (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Stanley Karson (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Kathryn Keeley (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Kenilworth Parkside Resident Management Corp. (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Michael F. Kieschnick (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Kresge Foundation (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Jeffrey Lant Associates (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Adrienne Lapella (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Lear's Magazine (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Morton Levy (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Lincoln-Lancaster Commission on the Staus of Women (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Legislation on women (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Sandy Livingston (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - LKL Productions (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Loan Funds, Financial Institutions (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Long Island University Small Business Development Center (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - L.A. Times (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Longman Group U.K. Lim. (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - FY 1983 Budget and Low Income Families (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Housing - Low Income (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Mainstream Access, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Management Team Consultants (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Manpower Demonstration Research Group (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Thea Marshall Communications (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Marymount Manhattan College (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Jewel Jackson McCabe (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Martha McKay (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Catherine McGowan (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Meeting Sites (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Metropolitan Economic Development Assoc. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Michigan House of Reps. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Mid Net News (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - MPSN (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Midwest Women's Center (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Mind "Your Own Business" at Home (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Miner and Fraser Public Affairs (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Minnesota Project (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Minority Women in Business (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Orgs. (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Mississippi Action for Community Education (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Julie Motz (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Ms Foundation (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - La MUJER OBRERA (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Fred Myer Charitable Trust (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Johnson Foundation - Wingspread Conferences (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - National Center for Religious Involvement (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - National Commission on Working Women (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - National Congress for Community Economic Development (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - National Congress of Neighborhood Women (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - National Council for International Visitors (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - National Council for Urban Economic Development (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - National Council for Research on Women (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - National Council on Crime and Delinquency (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - National Council on Negro Women (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - National Executive Service Corps (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - National Federation of Independent Business (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - National Female Advocacy Project (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - National Governor's Assoc. (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - National Institute of Women of Colour (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - National Jazz Service Organization (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - National Low Income Housing Coalition (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - National Minority Supplier Development Council Inc. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - National Neighborhood Reinvestment Conference (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - National Network of Grantmakers (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - National Network of Hispanic Women (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - National Project on Homebased Work (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - National Resource Center for Children in Poverty (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - National Women's Employment and Education (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - National Training and Info. Center (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - National Urban Coalition (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - National Urban Fellows (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - National Women's Health Network (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Native American Community Board (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - NAWBO - NYC (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Neighborhood Reinvestment (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - New Directions for Women (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - New Directions for Young Women (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - New Enterprise Training for Profits (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - New Ways to Work With Archives (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - New Enterprise Scheme (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - New Federal Theater (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - New Jersey Dept. of Community Affairs (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - New Ventures (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - New Views (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - NYC Comm. on the Status of Women (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - NYC Human Resource Admin. (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - New York County Lawyers Association (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - New York NOW Project Committee (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - "9-5" Office Workers (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - NGO (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - NY State Assembly (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - NY State Assembly Program Develop. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - NY Delegation (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - NY State Dept. of Commerce (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - NY State Division for Women (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - NY State Minority Business Development Convention (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - NY State Senate (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - NYU - Review of Law and Social Change (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Northshire Women in Business (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - NOW Long Island (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Oakland Women's Center (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - OECD (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Office of Economic Development (New Haven, CT) (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Office of International Trade (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Office of Management and Budget (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Ohio State University (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Omaha Business Tech. Center (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Operation Life (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Options (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Orange Co. Refugee Community Resources Opportunity Project (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Organization for Equal Education of the Sexes, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Pacific Business Center (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Patricia Palmeri (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Julia Parzen (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Passages, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Peace Corps (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Penn State (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Philanthropic Profiles (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Police Foundation (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Politics and Markets (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Project New (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Project Self-Sufficiency (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Project on the Status and Education of Women (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Public Interest Public Relations (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Public/Private Ventures (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Putting it All Together (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Marilyn Quinto (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Yolanda Quitman (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Quotable Quotes (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Ann Ramsay Necel Speech (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Ken Reardon (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Ingrid Reed (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Religious Network for Equality for Women (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Resource Center for Women (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Resource for Individual Women (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Dorothy Ridings (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Reports (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Ms. Francis Roelfsema (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Rocky Mountain Institute (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Rosenberg Foundation (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Barbara Rose (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Dr. Judy B. Rosener (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Sylvia Rowe (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - John Rozette/NY Assembly (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Nancy Rubin/Women baward. DEV. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Gilian Rudd (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Rural American Women (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Rural Women Entrepreneurs (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Rural Women (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Louise Rush (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Russell Sage Foundation (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Saint Francis College (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Saint Joseph College (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Phyllis A. Sanders (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Save the Children (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Schauffler, Marjorie Page Obit. (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Schlesinger Library (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Anne F. Scott (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Dean Seavers/Need (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Self Help Crafts (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Self-Sufficiency (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - SER Jobs for Progress, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Jill S. Heffield (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Shur Corp. (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Small Business (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Sherwood Forest Fund (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Smith College (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Alden Smith - Colbert Collection (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Clare Smith (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Stephanie Smith (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Dr. Susan R. Solomon (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - South Bronx (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - South Carolina (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - South Shore Bank (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Southern Women's Rural Network (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Spartenberg, SC Economic Dev. Corp. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Connie M. Spruill (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - S (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Stanford (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Stanford Alumni Association (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Stanford Center for Entrepreneurship (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Stanford Gardner Fellowship (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Stanford Mid-Peninsula Urban Coalition (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Stanford Public Service Center (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Karl Stauber (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Catherine N. Stratton (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Suzanne Strickland (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Myra H. Strober (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Martha Stuart Communications (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Spencer Stuart (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Swarthmore (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Jannette Tappan (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Charlotte Taylor - Net/Pro (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Transitions (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - U.S. Congress (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Dept. of Energy (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Dept. of Housing and Urban Development (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Senate (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Women and Job/Statistics (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Women's Center for Education and Career Advancement (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Technical Assistance for Women Group (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Technology and Women's Employment (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Telecommunications Cooperative Network (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Irene Tinker (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Tradewwoman (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Trade Trax (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Transition House (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Transitional Housing, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Transnational Network for Appropriate Alternative Technologies (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Trusteeship Institute (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Turquoise Records (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - UNDP (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - United Church of Christ (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - United Methodist Church (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - University of Rhode Island (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - University of Washington (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Urban Institute (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Urban Neighborhood Investment Program (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Vanguard Communications (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Vermont Governor's Commission on the Status of Women (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Vision House - Elinor Hart (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Sylvia F. Villarreal, M.D. (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Viveza International, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Volunteers of America (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Fran Weiland (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Wellesley Center for Research on Women (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Western Center on Domestic Violence (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Gardenia White (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - White House: Conference on Small Business (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - White House: Conference on Small Business (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - WICS (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - WOW Newsletter (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Wildcat Service Corp. (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Charles Wilson (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Windham Foundation (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Wingspread Journal (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Wisconsin Community Development (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Wisconsin Women's Council (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Kathleen Wiseman (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - WAF (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - WNYC AM 83 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Women and Employment, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Women Business Owners of VT (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Women Corporate Directors (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Women Employed (Box 12, Folder 9)